family I'm feeling pretty
familia Tengo un cabreo bastante
pissed off today And it's because I just started
importante hoy Y es que justo Me acabo
recording This video and I
de poner a grabar Este vídeo y me
find that YouTube has put
encuentro con que YouTube me ha plantado
an age restriction on yesterday's video
una restricción de edad en el vídeo de
on the video about
ayer en el vídeo sobre el fallecimiento
Liam Pain's death The truth is that these
de liam pain la verdad es que estas
things really annoy me The video
cosas me fastidian muchísimo el vídeo
was around 70,000 views
iba por unas 70.000 visitas
approximately and suddenly boom They
aproximadamente y de repente pum La han
cut it I know it's not your
cortado sé que ustedes no tenéis la
fault I'm really sorry to be pissed off
culpa Lo siento mucho estar [__]
but I am pretty pissed off with
pero sí que estoy bastante [__] con
YouTube because I have reviewed the video, I have
YouTube porque he revisado el vídeo he
reviewed the rules, I have reviewed what
revisado las normas he revisado qué se
could be fixed and when I sent the
podía arreglar y cuando he mandado la
appeal after a few seconds they
apelación a los pocos segundos me han
answered rejecting it and the truth is
contestado rechazándola y la verdad es
that I don't believe the fact that
que me creo bastante poco el hecho de
a human being has reviewed that
que un ser humano haya revisado eso De
Really manually so well at the
verdad manualmente así que bueno de
moment I'm fighting with the
momento estoy peleándome con el chat de
YouTube chat I'm going to try to fix it it makes me
YouTube voy a intentar solucionarlo me
really angry because you know that
da mucho coraje porque ya sabéis que
these videos require a lot of work not
estos vídeos tienen mucho curro no
only from me but from the whole team
solamente mío sino de todo el equipo
but while I have uploaded the video I have
pero de mientras he subido el vídeo he
uploaded the video again with some
vuelto a subir el vídeo con algún que
patches, some fixes
otro parche algún que otro arregl yo
so that it doesn't happen again also in
para que no vuelva a pasar también en
part from now on we will be
parte a partir de ahora pues tendremos
more careful with some words with
más cuidado con algunas palabras con
some topics and use eh keywords I
algun temas y utilizar eh palabras clave
don't know the truth is that it's something
No lo sé la verdad es que es una cosa
that I don't like it has happened to me other
que no me gusta me ha pasado Ya otras
times at the moment that they put an
veces en el momento que te ponen una
age restriction on you you can appeal because they do
restricción de edad ya puedes apelar que
n't review it or whatever The
es que no lo revisan o sea Siempre me
same thing always happens to me once on
pasa lo mismo en una ocasión en
telesalseo it happened to me because Marina was
telesalseo me pasó porque Marina estaba
smoking in a live show they sent me the
fumando en un directo me mandaron la
age restriction I cut that piece
restricción de edad corté ese trozo
before sending the appeal and they
antes de enviar la apelación y te la
rejected it after a few seconds I mean it
rechazan a los pocos segundos o sea eso
's like automated to reject it and
está como automatizado para rechazarlo y
[ __ ] it pumpa la sprouta another
a tomar por culo pumpa la brota otra
restriction in this video let's see as I
restricción en este vídeo a ver como os
told you okay for now what I've done
he dicho vale de momento lo que he hecho
has been upload a version with some
ha sido subir una versión con algunas
censorship and such so that YouTube doesn't
censuras y tal para que YouTube no se
get stupid Oops I said stupid too and I would
ponga tonto Ups he dicho tonto también y
really appreciate it if you
de verdad os agradecería todo que os
stopped by the video even if it's just to
pasáis por el vídeo aunque sea para
give it a like comment and all that
darle like comentar y todas esas
stuff I'm going to wait to see if I can
cosillas voy a esperar a ver si consigo
fix it and if not then I'll probably
solucionarlo y si no pues seguramente
delete the one with the restriction
eliminaré el que tiene la restricción
so well if you can stop by
así que bueno si os podéis pasar por
there leave a comment leave the like and
allí dejar un comentario dejar el like y
all that  little things in the new I would
todas esas cosillas en el nuevo os lo
appreciate it and today I'm going to update you a
agradecería y hoy os voy a actualizar un
little on Didi's situation we have
poco la situación de Didi que tenemos
some news to discuss also
algunas novedades que comentar también
tell you that since I have
deciros que como este fin de tengo la
my sister's wedding this weekend I'm going to leave another
boda de mi hermana os voy a dejar otro
video uploaded that you will have uh
videíto subido que lo tendréis eh
probably I don't know if tomorrow Saturday or you
probablemente no sé si mañana sábado o
will have it today in the next few
lo tendréis hoy mismo en las próximas
hours but since I'm going to be a bit out of
horas pero como voy a estar un poco de
sorts then I'll try to leave
aquella manera pues intentaré dejar el
as much content as possible so that you don't
máximo de contenido posible para que no
notice my absence okay you know that
noté mi ausencia vale ya sabéis que el
Didi's case is pending until May
caso de Didi está en trámite hasta mayo
of next year until May 2025
del año que viene hasta mayo del 2025
which is supposed to be the expected date
que se supone que es la fecha esperada
in which the trial is going to take place at the
en la que va a tener lugar el juicio de
moment Halloween is approaching I do
momento se acerca la fecha de Halloween
n't know what you're going to do I'm looking for
no sé qué Vais a hacer yo ando buscando
something to do for that long weekend the truth
algo que hacer para ese puente la verdad
is I can't think of anything and the little
es que no se me ocurre nada y lo poco
that I've thought of is all very expensive
que se me ha ocurrido está todo carísimo
but yes there are a lot of people who are already
pero sí que hay mucha gente que se la
coming up with it and we already know what the
está ingeniando ya y ya sabemos cuál van
most popular costumes are going to be some
a ser los disfraces más demandados hay
years they are Harley Quinn other years they are into
años que son la Harley Quinn otros años
the Joker  Last year it
que les dan por el Joker el año pasado
was Daniel Sancho's And this year It
fue de Daniel Sancho Y en este año
seems that people want to
Parece ser que la gente se quiere
dress up as baby oil
disfrazar de aceite
[Music]
[Música]
Johnson Last people are linking the link just
Johnson Last people ar link thek just
ordering a new one for my boy cuz he hit
ordering a New One For My Boy Cuz he hit
me he said he didn't see the link so I
me he said he didn't see the link so I
just put the new link on this video for y
Just put the new link on this video for
feel me get y the top five costume of
y feel me get y the top Five costume of
2024 no baby oil included Man but yeah
2024 no baby oil included Man but yeah
here's the new link for anybody That's
here's the new link for anybody That's
still trying to grab up the mas all
Still trying to grab up the mas all
right so when you pop up to the part you
right so when you pop up to the Part you
supposed to pull up just like this feel
supposed to Pull up Just like this feel
me pull up just like this knock on the
me Pull up Just like this knock on the
door hold the baby oil up to the people
door Hold the baby oil up To The People
youo stupid bro in the last few hours
youo Stupid bro en las últimas horas ha
a new accusation has come to light It
salido a la luz una nueva acusación más
seems that we're going to a new accusation and
Parece ser que vamos a acusación nueva y
a new complaint per day from a boy who
a Nueva denuncia por día de un chico
attended in early May
asistente a principios de mayo de
1998 who apparently was invited by
1998 que al parecer Pues fue invitado de
chance to a Didi White party, that
medio casualidad a una White party de
is, we are no longer talking about the
Didi o sea estamos hablando ya no de las
Freak Party but now also about the
Freak Party sino ahora también de las
white parties at the moment the name of the
fiestas blancas de momento el nombre del
kid remains anonymous the
chaval se mantiene en el anonimato las
authorities of  moment they have decided to
autoridades de momento han decidido
protect his privacy he was invited to
proteger su intimidad fue invitado a
this party along with 200 other people
esta fiesta junto a otras 200 personas
as you know the dress code at
como ya sabéis el código de vestimenta
these parties is to wear white and The
Estas fiestas es ir de blanco y El
Kid at that time being 16 years old who
Chaval en ese momento con 16 años que
also had the dream of dedicating himself to
además tenía el sueño de dedicarse a la
music saw it as an opportunity
música pues lo vio como una oportunidad
to make contacts meet people and look
de hacer contactos conocer gente y Mira
where In one of these he was
tú por dónde En una de estas que estaba
looking for a bathroom he was walking down the hallway
buscando un baño iba por el pasillo
bumping into people until
chocándose con la gente hasta que de
suddenly he ran into
repente dio con
Didi Didi stopped him according to this
Didi Didi lo paró según cuenta este
boy well not so young but
muchacho bueno ya no tan muchacho pero
young of the time at the time Didi
muchacho de la época en su momento Didi
became interested in him asked him what he
se interesó por él le dijo que a qué se
wanted to do and basically Didi
quería dedicar y prácticamente Didi le
came to tell him that in the world of
vino a decir que en el mundo de la
music to be successful you only have to
música para tener éxito solamente habría
appear to be successful I mean he took that
que aparentar ser exitoso O sea que tení
more into account than the talent that
más en cuenta eso que el talento que
nobody else could have it's also a little
pudiera tener nadie también es un poco
true I mean I believe this and the
verdad o sea esto me lo creo y lo
next thing you're going to hear is what
siguiente que Vais a escuchar es lo que
according to the boy Didi told him
según el muchacho Didi le dijo a
next the only thing that mattered was
continuación lo único que importaba era
having the right look for the
tener el aspecto adecuado para la
industry he supposedly said coms before
industria dijo supuestamente coms antes
ordering do to lower his
de ordenarle a do que se bajar a los
pants so that the producer could
pantalones para que el productor pudiera
inspect it com supposedly
inspeccionarlo com supuestamente lo
called it a rite
llamó un rito de
according to this person's account, the ritual that he had to go through
según cuenta Esta persona ese ritual por
to be approved
el que tenía que pasar para ser aprobado
by Didy was to drop his pants so that
por didy era bajarse los pantalones para
Didy could see his penis and that's what happened
que didy le viera el nepe y así sucedió
immediately after Didi told him
inmediatamente después pues Didi le dijo
okay approved my agent will call you and she
vale aprobado ya te llamará mi agente
also comments that at that party there
además también comenta que en esa fiesta
were a lot of celebrities like
había muchas celebridades Como por
Leonardo DiCaprio who at that
ejemplo Leonardo DiCaprio que en aquel
time was super top he had just
momento era super top acababa de
hit the movie Titanic I don't know what you
triunfar la película Titanic no sé qué
think about this accusation but it
pensáis sobre esta acusación pero a mí
seems pretty weak to me and it's not to
me parece bastante flojita y no es por
justify it obviously if this happened
justificarla evidentemente si esto pasó
100% and it's real then it would be disgusting not
a 100% es real pues estaría asqueroso no
like everything we've heard during
como todo lo que hemos escuchado durante
all these videos that we're making
todos estos vídeos que estamos haciendo
But honestly I see it pretty
Pero sinceramente lo veo bastante
weak that they can condemn you for
flojito que te puedan condenar por una
something that is a testimony which is the
cosa que es un testimonio que es la
word of someone simply with the
palabra de alguien simplemente con la de
people that are there right now jumping on the
gente que hay ahora mismo subiéndose al
bandwagon inventing stories and you're
carro inventándose historia y me estás
denouncing me 30 years later I mean how are
denunciando 30 años después O sea cómo
you going to condemn someone for what they did
vas a condenar a alguien por lo que hizo
30 years ago without any kind of proof and
hace 30 años sin ningún tipo de prueba y
only your word and besides that's not
solamente tu palabra y además que ni
even disgusting
siquiera es tampoco es asqueroso
obviously it's serious because if  we are
evidentemente es grave porque si estamos
talking about a minor
estamos hablando de un menor
obviously it would be abuse but I
evidentemente sería un abuso pero yo
think that right now with all the
creo que ahora mismo con todas las
accusations that Didi has there are countless
acusaciones que tiene Didi hay infinidad
more serious things to be able to condemn
de cosas más graves para poder condenar
them they don't need this one that can be
les no necesitan esta que se pueden
proven and that can be demonstrated and that would
probar y que se pueden demostrar y que
also include assaults
además incluirían pues agresiones
struggles blood crimes
forcejeos delitos de sangre delitos de
sex crimes according to this boy what Didi did
sexo según este chico lo que hizo Didi
was look at his penis as I already told you I mean it's
fue mirarle en nepe que ya os digo O sea
not to take away from it obviously it
no es por quitarle peso evidentemente
would be abuse But all the stories
sería un abuso Pero todas las historias
that we are hearing in the
que estamos escuchando en los vídeos
previous videos there are many of them that are
anteriores hay muchas de ellas que están
more supported by evidence and let's say that there
más sustentadas en pruebas y digamos que
is more violence in this case Didi and
hay más violencia sobre este caso Didi y
her defense are asking for it to be
su defensa lo que está pidiendo es que
revealed who the victim is in order to
se revele Quién es la víctima para poder
prepare a defense to me this request
preparar una defensa a mí esta petición
seems logical and normal I mean having to
me parece lógica y normal o sea tener
go to trial and find
que llegar a juicio y encontrarse con
that accusation and defend yourself on the
esa acusación y defenderse sobre la
fly the truth is that it is a bit
marcha la verdad es que es un poco
complicated especially when we are
complicado sobre todo cuando estamos
talking about something from 30 years ago I mean
hablando de algo de hace 30 años o sea
I imagine that it would be a crime for you to
me imagino que sí será delito el que tú
ask a minor to show you their
le pidas a un menor que te enseñe el
penis but of course I don't know to what extent
nepe pero claro No sé yo hasta qué punto
30 years later they can  to condemn for it
30 años después pueden condenar por ello
I rather see it as a testimony
yo más bien lo veo como un testimonio
that if it has veracity Well, it could
que de tener veracidad Pues podría
support the other causes that are being
apoyar las otras causas que se están
reported and that perhaps are not
denunciando y que a lo mejor no están
prescribed and it is thus impossible without
prescritas y está así es imposible sin
knowing the name of the victim not
saber el nombre de la víctima ni
even for Didi's lawyers to
siquiera para los abogados de Didi
prepare a defense So I
preparar una defensa Así que yo me
imagine that this request will be
imagino que esta petición sí se la
accepted what they continue to not accept
aceptarán la que continúan sin aceptarle
under any circumstances is the request to
bajo ningún concepto es la petición de
reject the video where Didi is seen
rechazar el vídeo donde se ve a Didi
brutally aggravating ki and well
agendo brutalmente a ki y bueno
Likewise It is that you know that this case
Igualmente Es que sabéis que este caso
well, there is not going to be condemned because this
pues no se va a condenar porque este
case is already closed ki's case was
caso ya está cerrado el caso de ki quedó
closed in a million dollar agreement and
cerrado en un acuerdo millonario y
evidently you cannot judge
evidentemente ente no se puede juzgar
the same thing twice and the only reason they
dos veces la misma cosa y para lo único
are presenting the video is to
que están presentando el vídeo es para
have a little more context about
tener un poco más de contexto sobre
who this guy is and how he acts and
quién es este tipo y cómo actúa y para
well allege a little the aggressiveness he
bueno alegar un poco la agresividad que
has and how he moves no And how
tiene y cómo se mueve no Y cómo se
La Movida is handled that to me the fact that they
maneja La Movida que a mí el hecho de
had rejected the video well I did not care at all I
que hubieran rechazado el vídeo pues me
was telling you
daba un poco igual os lo estuve diciendo
in previous videos it seems absurd to me
en vídeos anteriores me parece absurdo
that this was canceled  video as evidence
que se cancelara ese vídeo como prueba
when they can simply provide Well,
cuando Sencillamente pueden aportar Pues
that the media itself has echoed
que los propios medios se han hecho Eco
the content of that video, that is,
del contenido de ese vídeo o sea todo el
everyone knows what's in that video, we've all
mundo sabe lo que hay en ese vídeo todos
seen it, so they should remove it
lo hemos visto entonces que lo retiren
as evidence, that they take away its validity as
como prueba que le quiten validez como
evidence Well then, well, I'm bringing you
prueba Bueno pues ya está pues te llevo
some news where they talk about what happened
una noticia donde hablan de lo que pasó
in that video and that there is evidence that
en ese vídeo y que hay pruebas que la
proves it, the actress Aoki Lee Simons, daughter
acreditan la actriz Aoki Lee simons hija
of Russell Simon, pioneer of the
de Russell Simon pionero del género del
Rap genre, asked to stop the harassment against
Rap pidió parar con el acoso contra las
Didi's daughters, especially the youngest ones, you
hijas de Didi especialmente las menores
know that the twins are 17 years old
ya sabéis que las gemelas tienen 17 años
and currently Well, they are receiving
y actualmente Pues están recibiendo
a lot of harassment on social networks because there are many
mucho acoso en redes porque hay mucha
people writing to them asking them to
gente escribiéndole pidiéndoles que se
speak out to condemn their father,
pronuncien para condenar a su padre a mí
this seems [ __ ] crazy to me And in this
esto me parece una [__] locura Y en este
case, notice that I agree with
caso Fíjate que si estoy de acuerdo con
what this girl is asking for at the
lo que está pidiendo esta chica de
moment The Criminal that we know is Didi,
momento El Criminal que sepamos es Didi
not the girls, and putting them in a difficult position and
no las niñas y ponerlas en el aprieto y
harassing them, the truth is that it is
acosarlos la verdad es que es de estar
a little sick What do you want me to tell you,
un poco malito Qué quieres que te diga
the FBI has justified how violent
el FBI tiene justificado lo violento que
Didi is with many things, no  just
es Didi con muchas cosas no solamente
with the video of almost for example there
con el vídeo de casi por ejemplo también
is also an episode with
hay un episodio con el entrenador de
his son's football coach in which
fútbol americano de su hijo en el que
well in a game it turns out that he
bueno en un partido Resulta ser como que
sanctioned him let's say he punished him on the
lo sancionó digamos que lo castigó en el
bench and Didi after the game
banquillo y Didi después del partido se
went to the coach's office and from what they
fue a la oficina del entrenador y por lo
say he became so aggressive that
que dicen se puso tan agresivo que tuvo
the police who were
que intervenir la policía que estaba por
nearby had to intervene not only because of shouts
allí cerca no solamente por gritos
insults or anything like that but
insultos ni nada por el estilo sino que
apparently he even injures
por lo visto llegó a hacerle lesiones
the coach and the intern with a car key
con una llave de coche al entrenador y
and also apparently
al pasante y además también por lo visto
to finish feeling comfortable he grabbed
para terminar de quedarse a gusto cogió
a weight a gym weight I mean
una pesa una pesa de gimnasio me refiero
and threw it at him when leaving luckily it didn't hit him
y se la lanzó al irse por suerte no le
But anyway the scare of what
llegó a dar Pero bueno el susto de lo
you have no I don't know if you knew that
tien no no sé si sabíais que el suegro
Justin Bieber's father-in-law or rather hiley
de Justin Bieber o sea el padre de hiley
Bieber's father Stephen balding is the brother of
Bieber Stephen balding es el hermano de
al Balvin whether al Balvin is the uncle or rather
al Balvin sea al Balvin es el tío o sea
Justin Bieber's wife In the end it
de la mujer de Justin Bieber Al final
all stays in the family But anyway the
todo queda en familia Pero bueno La
Movida Is that this man in the last few
Movida Es que este hombre en los últimos
days has made some statements about the
días ha dado unas declaraciones sobre la
current situation that Justin is going through
actual situación por la que está pasando
and also applauding his daughter
Justin y además aplaudiendo a su hija
for being mainly responsible for helping
por ser principal responsable de ayudar
Justin get up in his worst moment
a Justin a levantarse en su peor momento
Uh to help him survive you know and Uh
Uh to help him survive you know and Uh
their happiness and their well-being and
their happiness and their wellbeing and
their Health is is is obvious more
their Health is is is obvious more
obviously Now better than ever and It's interesting
obviously Now better than ever and It's
You Say that Because I think
interesting You Say that Because I think
He's been One of the bravest artists
He's been One of the bravest artists
Ever there are Times when he could have
Ever there are Times when he could have
followed the record companies like Push
followed the record companies like Push
to carry on touring he stopped and said
to carry on touring he stopped and said
I need to do this mental Health he said I
I need to do this mental Health he said
need to check out for my mental Health
I need to check out for my mental Health
there are not many artists  he l the way
there are not many artists he l the way
i'd say for arti to say stop I need to
i'd say for arti to say stop I need to
Focus on my well-being would Would you
Focus on my wellbeing would Would you
reflect on that Because that must be
reflect on that Because that must be
Great To Know as A
Great To Know as A
grandfather early On meeting Justin
grandfather early On meeting Justin
Getting To Know him you know I I hung
Getting To Know him you know I I hung
out with him a bit before I said he
out with him a bit before I said he
could marry my
could marry my
daughter but What One of the simple
daughter but What One of the simple
things I told him was you know you decide You
things I told him was you know you
're
decide You're
normal you decide you and haey Will decide
normal you decide you and haey Will
You're normal either you can Drive
decide You're normal either you can
yourself and paparazzi drives you
Drive yourself and paparazzi drives you
crazy
crazy
the singer landon barker who was
el cantante landon barker que Fue
canceled in the  last weeks Because he
cancelado en las últimas semanas Porque
made a
hizo una parodia de las fiestas de la
Didi's White parties parody has come out to
White parties de Didi ha salido a
apologize because people jumped on him
disculparse porque la gente se le echó
for the inappropriateness of the
encima por lo inapropiado de la
joke let's see The kid went out to party to
broma a ver El chaval salió de fiesta a
celebrate his birthday with friends and given
celebrar su cumpleaños con los amigos y
the viral topic of the
tal y como estaba el tema viral del
moment, well, they all dressed in
momento no pues se vistieron todos de
white and not only do they wear white but they
blanco y no sol se visan de blanco sino
also went around with a little bottle of
que además iban con una botellita
Johnson &amp; Johnson in their hands parodying the
Johnson en la mano parodiando la
situation of did's abuse The guy
situación de los abusos de did El chico
has come out to justify himself practically
ha salido a justificarse prácticamente
with some excuses that, in my opinion, are quite
con unas excusas para mi gusto bastante
absurd notth Part myth Part next Now
absurdas notth Part myth Part next Now
happ all myth and it's
happ all myth and
a Birthday Party Tonight you guys Want To Come To
is a Birthday Party Tonight you guys
Party said Give Us Table
Want To Come To Party said Give Us Table
and bottle make we're all to we're like
and bottle make we're all to we're like
21 sea contradicts himself saying that it wasn't
21 sea se contradice diciendo que no era
his birthday but it was it was the
su cumpleaño pero si lo era era la
official celebration but then IB went to
celebración oficial pero luego lo IB a
celebrate it
celebrar de manera
officially I didn't know was going on right
oficial I didn't know was going on right
away It was an environment and all I
away It was a environment and all I
could really see was another Table
could really see was another Table
having flashing bottles Being
having flashing bottles Being
then they out to Our Table and That's
then they out to Our Table and That's
When II no they have light up baby oil I
When II no they have light up baby oil I
didn't pick  up the bottle once And I did not condone
didn't pick up the bottle once And I did
I just Club
not condone I just Club
Cele that not everyone was wearing white that
Cele que no todos iban de blanco que
some were wearing a jacket and that the
algunos se ponían una chaqueta y que el
fact that they coincided in white
hecho de que coincidieran en lo blanco
was a coincidence and that the bottle he was
era casualidad y que la botella que
carrying in his hand as they were dark
llevaba en la mano como estaban oscur
that he didn't even know it was a
que no sabía ni siquiera que era una
bottle seen Pedro sanche use
botella visto a Pedro sanche utilizar
lies and excuses better than
mentiras y excusas mejores que
[Music]
[Música]
this
esta
formant I don't understand it very well I don't
formant yo no lo entendido muy bien No
know if you can refute what's
sé si ustedes podéis refutar lo que está
happening but come on
pasando pero vamos prácticamente está
the guy is practically saying that he didn't know that they had
diciendo el tipo que no sabía que habían
put little lights in the Johnson bottle
metido lucecitas a la botella Johnson
to turn them on at the party and dance in a
para encenderlas en la fiesta y bailar
sense man you made an
sentido tío has hecho una broma
inappropriate joke and that's it's not a big deal it
inapropiada y ya está tampoco pasa nada
's not the most serious thing in the world I
tampoco es lo más grave del mundo
also tell you in the last few days
también te digo en los últimos días
this photograph was also leaked it doesn't
también se filtró esta fotografía no
seem to be from a security camera in which we
parece ser de una cámara de seguridad en
can see Jennifer Lopez with
la que podemos ver a Jennifer López con
Didi in which it seems that they are leaving an
Didi en la que parece que salen de una
orgy and well you have sent me
[__] y bueno me habéis mandado
this photograph a lot You have
muchísimo esta fotografía Me la habéis
blown up Instagram with this photograph
petado el Instagram con esta fotografía
the truth is that I almost know the little
la verdad casi que me conozco ya los
nipples of those two in the back no no
pezoncitos de esos dos de atrás no no
put that because well they're going to
pongas eso porque es que bueno me van a
censor me Well yeah come on go Take it up the ass
censurar Bueno sí venga va Toma por culo
I know Soto's nipples that's it I'm going to
me conozco los pezones de Soto ya está
play it, I don't give a damn today I'm
me la juego me la sudo todo hoy estoy
very pissed off with the [ __ ] video that
muy [__] con el [__] vídeo que me
they removed from me it's a montage okay or so I haven't
han quitado es un montaje vale o sea no
commented on it because it's a montage the
lo he comentado porque es un montaje la
photo is real but this would be the
foto sí que es real pero esta sería la
original face let's see
cara original a ver está bien montada la
Jennifer Lopez's is well staged I'm not saying no but
de Jennifer López no te digo que no pero
well let's see It's still an orgy No what
bueno a ver Igualmente es una [__] No
happens is that we take Jennifer Lopez
lo que pasa que sacamos a Jennifer López
out of the equation precio muir an ex
de la ecuación preció muir una ex
Playboy bunny from many years ago has
conejita Playboy de hace muchos años ha
come out to say that she also
salido a relatar que también estuvo
attended Didi's parties and that
asistiendo a fiestas de Didi y que
Didi also attended the parties at the
también Didi asistía a las fiestas en la
Playboy mansion according to her the parties
mansión Playboy según ella las fiestas
at both houses were very different
de ambas casas eran muy diferentes Ya
Since at the owner's Playboy Mansion
que en las de La Mansión Playboy del
all the people looked of legal
dueño todas las personas se veían
age well you know what
mayores de edad en fin ya sabéis lo que
a Playboy party was and however at
era una fiesta Playboy y sin embargo en
Didi's parties Well the atmosphere was
la fiestas de Didi Pues el ambiente era
more murky you could
más turbio se podían encontrar menores
even find minors there as we have already
de edad incluso por ahí como ya hemos
mentioned in previous videos And people
comentado en vídeos anteriores Y a gente
very young getting high so I I was aware of
muy joven drogándose so I I was aware of
the didy cameras around the home but I never Saw
the didy cameras around the home but I
them you see so his cameras
never Saw them you see so his cameras
Maybe Had been a little bit more
Maybe Had have been a little bit more
hidden but hug hef cameras were very
hidden but hug hef cameras were very
very old school So You could see them
very old school So You could see them
they were like right there You Know
they were like right there You Know
so when you hear about the allegations
so when you hear about the allegations
and What's happened to these celebrities
and What's happened to these celebrities
and then you know Being in the moment and
and then you know Being in the moment
forgetting their cameras there and
and forgetting their cameras there and
doing the things that they've done it's
doing the things that they've done it's
very easily done I felt there was Always a
very easily done I felt there was Always
very well When I Met  him I
a a very well When I When I Met him I
felt When I got close to him I felt he
felt When I got close to him I felt he
Had very Bad Energy I felt like his
Had very Bad Energy I felt like his his
whole aura was off you know I didn't I didn't
whole aura was off you know I didn't I
you know get too close to him I did
didn't you know get too close to him I
n't hug him or Any Thing but I was
didn't hug him or Any Thing but I was
talking to him and he was you know he has
talking to him and he was you know he
a very strange Inner Circle I don't
has a very strange Inner Circle I don't
think anyone anyone of them speak up to
think anyone anyone of them speak up to
him they will never say no to him
him they will never say no to him
Imagine we're in an atmosphere Where
Imagine we're in an atmosphere Where
people Don't Say no to you ever So The
people Don't Say no to you ever So The
hugh hefna parties and  the diddy parties
hugh hefna parties and the diddy parties
have the same formula  It's the same
have the same formula It's the same
formula It's a lot of Uh naked Half naked
formula It's a lot of Uh naked Half
girls there's a lot of Sex going
naked girls there's a lot of Sex going
on there's people hooking up Uh there's
on there's people hooking up Uh there's
a lot of drug taking and there's a lot
a lot of drug taking and there's a lot
of drinking and they They are so similar
of drinking and they They are so similar
in that aspect The only difference is
in in that aspect The Only difference is
I remember seeing children at didy Part
I remember seeing children at didy Part
Never at House also des lie a
Never at House también des mentir un
creepy pat or conspiracy theory very
creepy pat o teoría de Conspiración muy
crazy and real that is out there circulating on
loca e real que hay por ahí rulando en
social networks okay a fake news in
redes sociales vale una fake news de
fact it has gone too viral both
hecho se ha hecho demasiado viral tanto
on Twitter and Facebook some
en Twitter como en Facebook unas
alleged statements by jiden Smith
supuestas declaraciones de jiden Smith
accusing his father Will of selling him to
acusando a su padre Will de venderlo a
Didi in fact all the videos we have
Didi de hecho todos los vídeos que hemos
made about Will is m and his son you
hecho sobre Will es m y su hijo me
have left comments asking me
habéis puesto comentarios preguntándome
about this and well when we have looked at it
por esto y bueno cuando lo hemos mirado
obviously there is no
evidentemente Pues no hay ninguna fuente
original truthful source or rather it has been like a
veraz original o sea ha sido como un
bit of a tikt it does not come from a tikt and word of
poco de un tikt no viene de un tikt y
mouth this is like
del boca a Boca esto es como la
butter not that jam by Ricky
mantequilla no la mermelada esa de Ricky
Martin but there is no proof that
Martin pero no existe ninguna prueba de
those versions exist Not even that
que existan esas versiones Ni esa
statement by jiden could not even
declaración de jiden ni siquiera podía
walk  I was short of breath I felt like
caminar me faltaba el aire sentía que
every step ripped a piece of my
cada paso me arrancaba un pedazo del
soul my father the person who should have been
alma mi padre la persona que debería
my refuge collaborated with him and
haber sido mi refugio colaboró con él y
together they destroyed every part of me not
juntos destruyeron cada parte de mí no
only did they ruin my life but they also
solo arruinaron mi vida sino que también
broke my brothers heart
quebraron el corazón de mi hermano
Justin Bieber I couldn't understand it I
Justin Bieber no podía comprenderlo no
couldn't understand how someone who claimed to
podía entender có alguien que decía
love us could cause so much pain Now all that's
amarnos podía causar tanto dolor Ahora
left is the silence of that
lo único que queda es el silencio de esa
betrayal that consumes me from
traición que me consume por
within Jiden Smith Jiden Smith revealed
dentro jiden Smith jiden Smith reveló
between bland the heartbreaking truth that he
entre sosos la desgarradora verdad que
has hidden for years the
ha ocultado durante años la figura
paternal figure who should have protected him
paterna que debería haberlo protegido lo
threw him into the Abyss leaving him alone and broken
lanzó al Abismo dejándolo solo y roto
with every word Jiden showed the
con cada palabra jiden mostró la
depth of his suffering confessing
profundidad de su sufrimiento confesando
that there were nights when he wished he wouldn't
que hubo noches en las que deseaban no
wake up just to escape the weight of
despertar solo para escapar del peso de
that betrayal the damage was so deep
esa traición el daño fue tan profundo
that he went so far as to ask with his heart in his
que llegó a pedir con el corazón en la
hand that his name be removed from his
mano que su nombre fuera eliminado de la
father's inheritance he doesn't want anything from
herencia de su padre no quiere nada de
him not his last name or his memories he just
él ni su apellido ni sus recuerdos solo
wants to forget even though he knows he will never be able to
quiere olvidar aunque sabe que jamás
and the truth is that it's disgusting
podrá hacerlo y la verdad que asco no
because one thing is conspiracies and
porque una cosa son las conspiraciones y
another thing is to cook up a story
otra cosa es currarse una noticia
make it up  statement not so
inventarte la declaración no tan
deep and with so many details and
profundamente y con tantos detalles y
narrate it as if you were giving a
narrarla como si estuvieras dando una
real news idiot whoever
noticia real [__] el que haya
did that no and well family what I said
hecho eso no y bueno familia lo dicho
let's leave the video here today in
vamos a dejar hoy por aquí el vídeo en
a few hours you will have another one or tomorrow Saturday
unas horas tendréis otro o mañana sábado
so subscribe to the Channel and stay
así que suscribiros al Canal y estaros
tuned to the Channel because we are going to upload
pendiente del Canal porque vamos a subir
a pretty good video also
un vídeo bastante Bueno también os
I ask you again please to go
vuelvo a pedir por favor que os paséis
to the video before this one so that
por el vídeo anterior a este para que
YouTube can position it again okay And let's
YouTube lo vuelva a posicionar vale Y a
see if you can take away my disappointment I send you
ver si me quitáis el disgusto os mando
a big kiss have a great
un beso muy fuerte que paséis un gran
weekend and until the next video
fin de semana y hasta el próximo vídeo
bye bye
chao chao